Contact

teresabloodworth@comcast.ne

www.linkedin.com/in/teresa-bloodworth-40676695 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Cardiothoracic Surgery
Patient Advocacy
Process Improvement

Languages

English

Certifications
CCRN

Teresa Bloodworth

MSN, RN, CCRN

Jacksonville, Florida

Summary

Experienced Clinical Coordinator with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Palliative Care, Databases, Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), Healthcare Management, and Healthcare. Strong healthcare services professional with a currently attending focused in Family Practice Nurse/Nursing from Chamberlain College of Nursing.

Experience

Florida Hospital CVICU December 2017 - Present (2 years 7 months) Orlando, Florida Area

UF Health Jacksonville
CVICU Clinical Coordinator
March 2015 - Present (5 years 4 months)
Cardiac and Thoracic Surgery STS Data Manager
CardioThoracic Surgery & post operative QA
Review and Develop protocols
Performance Improvement Initiatives
CVICU Quality Assurance
Patient Education

HCA
Registered Nurse
May 1988 - February 2015 (26 years 10 months)

Education

Chamberlain College of Nursing currently attending, Family Practice Nurse/Nursing · (2014 - 2019)

Chamberlain College of Nursing
Family Practice Nurse/Nursing · (2014 - 2016)